kabbage.com 2019-11-15

# Kabbage Legal | Kabbage

## Terms of Service

  * ## General & Acceptance

BY USING AND/OR VISITING THIS WEBSITE AND/OR USING THE _KABBAGE_ ™ SERVICES (specifically, inputting your user id in the space provided on various pages of the www.kabbage.com website, the "Services"), YOU SIGNIFY YOUR ASSENT TO BOTH THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS (the "Terms of Use" or "Agreement") AND THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF KABBAGE, INC.'S ("Kabbage") PRIVACY POLICY, WHICH ARE PUBLISHED VIA A LINK ON http://www.kabbage.com (the "Website"), AND WHICH ARE INCORPORATED HEREIN BY REFERENCE. If you do not agree to any of these terms, then please do not use the Website or the Services. Please note that your application for a funding account with _Kabbage_ is subject to a separate agreement that will be provided to you upon application. THESE TERMS OF USE DO NOT COVER YOUR FUNDING ACCOUNT APPLIED FOR THROUGH THE WEBSITE, unless otherwise stated herein. The use of the term _Kabbage_ herein includes Kabbage, Inc. and its affiliates, vendors, partners, agents and other personnel. In addition to all other agreements that may be provided to you, this Terms of Use Agreement sets forth the legally binding terms for your use of the Services and they shall apply to all users of the Website. By using the Services, you agree to be bound by this Agreement. You are only authorized to use the Services (regardless of whether your access or use is intended) if you agree to abide by all applicable laws and to this Agreement. PLEASE READ THIS AGREEMENT CAREFULLY AND SAVE IT. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH IT, YOU SHOULD LEAVE THE WEBSITE AND DISCONTINUE USE OF THE SERVICES IMMEDIATELY. IF YOU WISH TO USE OF THE SERVICES, YOU MUST READ THIS AGREEMENT. In order to participate in certain other services provided through the Website, you will be notified that you are required to agree to additional terms and conditions. _Kabbage_ may modify this Agreement from time to time and such modification shall be effective upon posting by _Kabbage_ on the Website. You agree to be bound to any changes to this Agreement when you use the Services after any such modification is posted. It is therefore important that you review this Agreement regularly upon each use of the Services to ensure you are updated as to any changes.

* * *

  * ## Section 1: Eligibility

Use of the Services is void where prohibited. By using the Services, you represent and warrant that (a) all application information you submit is truthful and accurate; (b) you will maintain the accuracy of such information; (c) you are 18 years of age or older; and (d) your use of the Services does not violate any applicable law or regulation. Your profile may be deleted and your Membership may be terminated without warning, if we believe, in our sole discretion, that you are less than 18 years of age.

* * *

  * ## Section 2: Provided Services

Subject to full compliance with the Terms of this Use Agreement, _Kabbage_ shall provide certain services related to the input of your marketplace ID(s) on various pages of the Website. The Services are provided by _Kabbage_ AS IS and _Kabbage_ assumes no responsibility for any failure in providing the Services to you. _Kabbage_ may change, suspend or discontinue any or all of the Services for any reason, at any time, including the availability of any products or services included within the Services. _Kabbage_ may also impose limits on all or any of the Services or restrict your access to parts or all of the Services without notice or liability. _Kabbage_ may include commercial opportunities or content in any _Kabbage_ product, services, image or webpage.

* * *

  * ## Section 3: General Undertakings

You accept sole responsibility for all of your activities using the Website, including your conduct on the site. You will not use the Services for any unauthorized or illegal purpose. You will be responsible for ensuring that you do not violate any laws of your jurisdiction, including but not limited to copyright laws. You will not upload or transmit viruses, worms or any other destructive code. You will not use bots to engage the Services.

* * *

  * ## Section 4: The Website

The Website may contain third party content about, and links to, third parties and their websites that are not owned or controlled by _Kabbage_. _Kabbage_ has no control over, and assumes no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third party content or websites or any of their contents. In addition, _Kabbage_ will not and cannot censor or edit the content of any third-party site. By using the Website, you expressly relieve _Kabbage_ from any and all liability arising from your use of any third-party website. Accordingly, we encourage you to be aware when you leave the Website and to read the terms and conditions and privacy policy of each other website that you visit.

* * *

  * ## Section 5: Website Access

A. Kabbage, Inc. hereby grants you permission to use the Website as set forth in this Terms of Use, provided that: (i) you will not alter or modify any part of the Website other than as may be reasonably necessary to use the Website for its intended purpose and/or in a manner allowed by _Kabbage_ ; and (ii) you will otherwise comply with the terms and conditions of these Terms of Service. B. In order to access some features of the Website, you will have to create an account. You may never use another's account without permission. When creating your account, you must provide accurate and complete information. You are solely responsible for the activity that occurs on your account, and you must keep your account password secure. You accept sole responsibility for keeping your password secure. You must notify _Kabbage_ immediately of any breach of security or unauthorized use of your account. Although _Kabbage_ will not be liable for your losses caused by any unauthorized use of your account, you may be liable for the losses of _Kabbage_ or others due to such unauthorized use.

* * *

  * ## Section 6: Fees & Payment

Some of the services offered on the Website may require the payment of fees, interest and other amounts ("Charged Services"). These services are subject to separate agreements into which you must enter prior to participating in such service. If you elect to sign up for Charged Services, you shall pay all applicable amounts, as described on the Website in connection with such Charged Services selected by you. _Kabbage_ reserves the right to change its prices and at any time, subject to applicable law. You authorize _Kabbage_ directly or through third parties, to make any inquiries it considers necessary to validate your account and financial information as provided while signing up for such Charged Services. All fees are exclusive of all taxes, levies, or duties imposed by taxing authorities, and you shall be responsible for payment of all such taxes, levies, or duties. You agree to pay for any such taxes that might be applicable to your use of the Services and payments made by you to _Kabbage_. Other amounts and the terms for payment of those amounts are described of specific application pages as you progress through your application (and from time to time thereafter).

* * *

  * ## Section 7: Intellectual Property Rights

The content on the Website (the "Content") and the Services are subject to copyright and other intellectual property rights under local and international laws conventions. To the best of its knowledge, _Kabbage_ uses only Content that it owns or is otherwise allowed and permitted for use by the owner/s of the copyrights and other intellectual property rights therein. Content on the Website is provided to you AS IS only and it may not be used, copied, reproduced, distributed, transmitted, broadcast, displayed, sold, licensed, or otherwise exploited for any other purposes whatsoever without the prior written consent of the respective owners. _Kabbage_ reserves all rights not expressly granted in and to the Website, Services and the Content. You agree to not engage in the use, copying, or distribution of any of the Content or Services other than expressly permitted herein for any commercial purposes. You agree not to circumvent, disable or otherwise interfere with security related features of the Website or features that prevent or restrict use of Services or copying of any Content or enforce limitations on use of the Website or any of the Services or Content therein.

* * *

  * ## Section 8: Third-Party Service Providers

Provide Accurate Information. You agree to provide true, accurate, current, and complete information about yourself and your accounts maintained at other web sites and you agree to not misrepresent your identity or your account information. You agree to keep your account information up to date and accurate.

Proprietary Rights. You are permitted to use content delivered to you through the Services only on the Services. You may not copy, reproduce, distribute, or create derivative works from this content. Further, you agree not to reverse engineer or reverse compile any of the Services technology.

Content You Provide. You are licensing to _Kabbage_ and its service providers ("Service Provider"), any information, data, passwords, materials or other content (collectively, "Content") you provide through or to the Services for the purpose of enabling _Kabbage_ and the Service Provider to provide you the Services. During the term of this Agreement, _Kabbage_ and the Service Provider may use, modify, display, distribute and create new material using such Content to provide the Services to you. By submitting Content, you automatically agree, or promise that the owner of such Content has expressly agreed that, without any particular time limit, and without payment of any fees, _Kabbage_ and the Service Provider may use the Content for the purposes set out above.

Third Party Accounts. By using the Services, you authorize _Kabbage_ and the Service Provider to access third-party sites designated by you, on your behalf, to retrieve information requested by you, and to register for accounts requested by you. For all purposes hereof, you hereby grant _Kabbage_ and the Service Provider a limited power of attorney, and you hereby appoint _Kabbage_ and the Service Provider as your true and lawful attorney-in-fact and agent, with full power of substitution and resubstitution, for you and in your name, place and stead, in any and all capacities, to access third- party internet sites, servers or documents, retrieve information, and use your information, all as described above, with the full power and authority to do and perform each and every act and thing requisite and necessary to be done in connection with such activities, as fully to all intents and purposes as you might or could do in person. YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT WHEN _KABBAGE_ OR THE SERVICE PROVIDER ACCESSES AND RETRIEVES INFORMATION FROM THIRD-PARTY SITES, _KABBAGE_ AND SERVICE PROVIDER ARE ACTING AS YOUR AGENT, AND NOT THE AGENT OR ON BEHALF OF THE THIRD PARTY. You agree that third- party account providers shall be entitled to reply on the foregoing authorization, agency and power of attorney granted by you. You understand and agree that the Services are not endorsed or sponsored by any third-party account providers accessible through the Services. You acknowledge that through the use of the Services, _Kabbage_ shall have access to your account credentials, including but not limited to login username and passwords.

* * *

  * ## Section 9: Warranty Disclaimer & Limitation of Liability

YOU AGREE THAT YOUR USE OF THE WEBSITE AND SERVICES SHALL BE AT YOUR SOLE RISK. TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, _KABBAGE_ , ITS OFFICERS, DIRECTORS, EMPLOYEES, AND AGENTS DISCLAIM ALL WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, IN CONNECTION WITH THE WEBSITE AND YOUR USE THEREOF. _KABBAGE_ MAKES NO WARRANTIES OR REPRESENTATIONS REGARDING THE ACCURACY OR COMPLETENESS OF THIS WEBSITE'S CONTENT OR THE CONTENT OF ANY SITES LINKED TO THIS SITE. IN NO EVENT SHALL _KABBAGE_ , ITS OFFICERS, MEMBERS, DIRECTORS, EMPLOYEES, OR AGENTS, BE LIABLE TO YOU FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, PUNITIVE, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES WHATSOEVER RESULTING FROM ANY (I) ERRORS, MISTAKES, OR INACCURACIES OF CONTENT OR SERVICES, (II) PERSONAL INJURY OR PROPERTY DAMAGE, OF ANY NATURE WHATSOEVER, RESULTING FROM YOUR ACCESS TO AND USE OF OUR WEBSITE, (III) ANY UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS TO OR USE OF OUR SECURE SERVERS AND/OR ANY AND ALL PERSONAL INFORMATION AND/OR OTHER INFORMATION STORED THEREIN, (IV) ANY INTERRUPTION OR CESSATION OF TRANSMISSION TO OR FROM OUR WEBSITE, (IV) ANY BUGS, VIRUSES, TROJAN HORSES, OR THE LIKE WHICH MAY BE TRANSMITTED TO OR THROUGH OUR WEBSITE BY ANY THIRD PARTY, AND/OR (V) ANY ERRORS OR OMISSIONS IN ANY CONTENT OR FOR ANY LOSS OR DAMAGE OF ANY KIND INCURRED AS A RESULT OF THE USE OF ANY CONTENT POSTED, EMAILED, TRANSMITTED, OR OTHERWISE MADE AVAILABLE VIA THE WEBSITE. THE FOREGOING LIMITATION OF LIABILITY SHALL APPLY TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW IN THE APPLICABLE JURISDICTION. _KABBAGE_ DOES NOT WARRANT, ENDORSE, GUARANTEE, OR ASSUME RESPONSIBILITY FOR ANY PRODUCT OR SERVICE ADVERTISED OR OFFERED BY A THIRD PARTY THROUGH THE _KABBAGE_ WEBSITE OR ANY HYPERLINKED WEBSITE OR FEATURED IN ANY BANNER OR OTHER ADVERTISING, AND _KABBAGE_ WILL NOT BE A PARTY TO OR IN ANY WAY BE RESPONSIBLE FOR MONITORING ANY TRANSACTION BETWEEN YOU AND THIRD-PARTY PROVIDERS OF PRODUCTS OR SERVICES. AS WITH THE PURCHASE OF A PRODUCT OR SERVICE THROUGH ANY MEDIUM OR IN ANY ENVIRONMENT, YOU SHOULD USE YOUR BEST JUDGMENT AND EXERCISE CAUTION WHERE APPROPRIATE.

* * *

  * ## Section 10: Indemnity

You agree to defend, indemnify and hold harmless _Kabbage_ , its parent corporation, officers, directors, employees and agents, from and against any and all claims, damages, obligations, losses, liabilities, costs or debt, and expenses (including but not limited to attorney's fees) arising from: (i) your use of and access to the Website; (ii) your violation of any term of these Terms of Use; (iii) your violation of any third party right, including without limitation any copyright, property, or privacy right; or (iv) your violation of any other terms applicable to your use of Charged Services. This defense and indemnification obligation will survive these Terms of Use and your use of the Website.

* * *

  * ## Section 11: Events Beyond Control

Under no circumstances shall _Kabbage_ be held liable for any delay or failure in this Website and/or any of the Services and/or information on the Website directly or indirectly resulting from, arising out of, relating to or in connection with events beyond the reasonable control of _Kabbage_ , including, without limitation, Internet failures, equipment failures, electrical power failures, strikes, labor disputes, riots, insurrections, civil disturbances, shortages of labor or materials, fires, floods, storms, earthquakes, explosions, acts of God, war, terrorism, intergalactic struggles, governmental actions, orders of courts, agencies or tribunals or non-performance of third parties. The provisions of this paragraph are in addition to, and not intended to limit or modify, the limitation of Limitation of Liability section as stipulated above.

* * *

  * ## Section 12: Assignment

These Terms of Use, and any rights and licenses granted hereunder, may not be transferred or assigned by you, but may be assigned by _Kabbage_ without restriction or limitations.

* * *

  * ## Section 13: General

You agree that: (i) the Website shall be deemed solely based in Georgia, USA; and (ii) the Website shall be deemed a passive website that does not give rise to personal jurisdiction over Kabbage, Inc., either specific or general, in jurisdictions other than Georgia. These Terms of Service shall be governed by the internal substantive laws of the State of Georgia, without respect to its conflict of laws principles. Any claim or dispute between you and Kabbage, Inc. that arises in whole or in part from the Website or the Services shall be decided exclusively by a court of competent jurisdiction located in Atlanta, Georgia. These Terms of Service, together with the privacy and any other legal notices and agreements published by Kabbage on the Website, shall constitute the entire agreement between you and Kabbage, Inc. concerning the Website. If any provision of these Terms of Use is deemed invalid by a court of competent jurisdiction, the invalidity of such provision shall not affect the validity of the remaining provisions of these Terms of Use, which shall remain in full force and effect. No waiver of any term of this these Terms of Use shall be deemed a further or continuing waiver of such term or any other term, and _Kabbage_ 's failure to assert any right or provision under these Terms of Use shall not constitute a waiver of such right or provision. YOU AND _KABBAGE_ AGREE THAT ANY CAUSE OF ACTION ARISING OUT OF OR RELATED TO THE WEBSITE MUST COMMENCE WITHIN ONE (1) YEAR AFTER THE CAUSE OF ACTION ACCRUES. OTHERWISE, SUCH CAUSE OF ACTION SHALL BE PERMANENTLY BARRED.

* * *

## Kabbage Privacy Policy

##### August 9th, 2019

  * ## General

Kabbage, Inc. (“ _Kabbage_ ”), its affiliates, and subsidiaries (collectively, “ _we_ ”, “ _us_ ” and “ _our_ ”) provide this Privacy Policy to the website visitors, users, and businesses that access services provided by or through Kabbage (collectively, “ _you_ ” or “ _your_ ”). This Privacy Policy applies when you access or use [www.kabbage.com](https://www.kabbage.com/) or any other website or application that links to or directly provides this Privacy Policy (collectively, the “ _Sites_ ”) and describes how we collect, store, use, share, and protect information about you to operate the Sites and make available business financial products and services (collectively with the Sites, the “ _Services_ ”). This Privacy Policy also describes your choices regarding certain information we collect about you. The terms of this Privacy Policy are incorporated into the Kabbage Terms of Service.

If you apply for or obtain a financial product or service where we function as a service provider for our bank partners, such as a _Kabbage_ ® Small Business Loan offered by Celtic Bank Corporation, any information that we collect from and about you will be on behalf of the bank partner.

* * *

  * ## The USA Patriot Act

IMPORTANT INFORMATION ABOUT PROCEDURES FOR OPENING AN ACCOUNT

To help the government fight the funding of terrorism, money laundering activities and other financial crimes, federal law requires all financial institutions to obtain, verify and record information that identifies each person who opens an account.

What this means for you: When you obtain a financial product or service offered by or in connection with our relationship with a financial institution, we may ask for your name, mailing address and other information or documentation, such as a copy of your driver’s license or other identifying documents, to verify your identity and otherwise comply with the applicable federal laws and regulations.

* * *

  * ## Information Collected

In connection with your use of the Services, we collect three types of information about you: Business Information, User Information, and General Information. Information from any of these categories may be linked with other information that we collect about you.  

    1.  _Business Information_. Business Information includes information regarding businesses that use or otherwise access the Services (“ _Customers_ ”). Business Information may also include information about your customers (i.e., businesses that have a commercial relationship or otherwise transact with Customers) if collected in connection with such Customer’s use or access of the Services. Business Information includes, but is not limited to (i) business name, address, email, and telephone number, (ii) company structure, (iii) industry type, (iv) incorporation date, (v) annual revenue, (vi) bank account information (e.g., average bank balance, bank statements, credit card statements), (vii) marketplace account information (e.g., transactions on PayPal, Shopify, Amazon), (viii) payment information (e.g., payment history, merchant category code, payment card number), (ix) business social network data (e.g., likes, posts, followers), (x) accounting information (e.g., Quickbooks), (x) vendor usage information (e.g., MailChimp), (xi) information regarding our transactions and experiences with the business, and (xiii) beneficial ownership information.

In the U.S., federal law requires us to collect and verify beneficial ownership information of our Customers. We collect this information to protect the U.S. financial system from financial crimes like money laundering, tax evasion, corruption, and fraud. Requiring the disclosure of key individuals who ultimately own or control the business helps law enforcement investigate and prosecute financial crimes. We will collect and maintain beneficial ownership information in compliance with this Privacy Policy.

    2.  _User Information_. User Information includes information about the owners, principals, and business representatives, such as: name, job title, user name(s), mailing address, email address, primary telephone number, date of birth, social security number, and FICO score. In addition, if you make payments through the Services, we may also collect information about your customers, such as payments or invoicing information, so we can provide the Services.
    3.  _General information_. General Information includes technical information such as information regarding your use of and interactions with the Sites. This General Information includes, but is not limited to, information about (i) your Internet connection, (ii) the equipment you use to access the Sites and usage details, (iii) your operating system, browser version and internet protocol (IP) address, (iv) your mobile device type, your device’s unique identifier, and your mobile network information, and (v) web pages, content, communications, or advertisements that you view or otherwise interact with, and (vi) referring/exit pages, clickstream data, and information that you search for using the Services.

* * *

  * ## How We Collect Your Information

    1.  _Information Provided by You_. We collect any information you provide when you use the Services. For example, we collect User Information and Business Information from you when you (i) register an account on the Sites, (ii) fill out forms or fields on the Sites, or (iii) complete an application for a product or service available through the Services. We also collect any information you may submit through communications with us by email, mail, text, telephone, facsimile or other means.

The Services allow us, upon your direction, to obtain User Information and Business Information from third party entities that your business maintains accounts with such as financial institutions, service providers, and social networking services. For example, we may obtain (i) transactional information about your business from financial institutions, (ii) information about your business’s engagement with customers from social networking services, and (iii) information about your business’s sales volume from service providers.

    2.  _Information We Collect When You Use Our Services_. We automatically collect General Information from your computer, mobile device or other device you use when you access the Services (including downloading and using a mobile application or accessing a mobile optimized Site), view content about the Services on a third-party website or open emails or links in emails from us. We, our business partners, or our service providers may use cookies or similar technologies to collect information. Cookies are small text files containing a string of alphanumeric characters. We may use both session cookies and persistent cookies. A session cookie disappears after you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser and may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the Services. Please review your web browser “Help” file to learn the proper way to modify your cookie settings. Please note that if you delete or choose not to accept cookies from the Service, you may not be able to utilize the features of the Services to their fullest potential. We also use cookies and similar technologies hosted by third parties on the Services. For instance, we use Google Analytics to collect and process certain analytics data. Google provides some additional privacy options described at [www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/) regarding Google Analytics’ cookies. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by such companies on an individual and aggregated basis.
    3.  _Information Received from Third Parties_. In the course of providing the Services, we may also collect additional Business Information or User Information from third parties, including, but not limited to: financial institutions, referral partners, identity verification services, card networks, vendors, mailing list providers, consumer reporting agencies, commercial credit bureaus and associations, fraud prevention agencies, and publicly available sources. We may combine this information with information we already have about you.

* * *

  * ## Use of Information

    1.  _Service-Related Usage_. We use the information we collect about and from you, both in a personally-identifiable form and in an aggregated or anonymized form, for a number of purposes, including for providing, supporting, promoting, and improving the Services. Such uses include:
      1. Enabling users to obtain products and services through the Services;
      2. Facilitating marketing, processing, servicing, and collections activities;
      3. Providing customer support;
      4. Understanding, customizing, and enhancing user experience;
      5. Providing targeted marketing and advertising;
      6. Determining your eligibility for the Services;
      7. Verifying your identity, conducting appropriate diligence, and keeping your information current;
      8. Creating an account connection between your account and a third-party account or platform;
      9. Sending notifications and information regarding the Services;
      10. Measuring and improving the performance and functionality of the Sites;
      11. Managing and protecting our information technology infrastructure;
      12. Administering and managing the security of the Sites;
      13. Developing new products and services; and
      14. Compiling, using, researching, analyzing, and generating data analytics reports to better understand our Customers and to improve the Services;
    2.  _Communications_. We may communicate with you using the information collected (i) for customer service, (ii) to provide you with updates or information relating to the Services, or (iii) to conduct surveys and collect feedback about the Services.
    3.  _Marketing and Advertising_. We may use the information we collect for marketing and advertising purposes, such as providing you with promotional materials that may be useful, relevant, valuable, or otherwise of interest to you. Where required under applicable law, we will obtain your prior opt-in consent to send you electronic marketing communications. To learn more about your choices regarding interest-based advertising and cross-device tracking, please see the Third-Party Information Collection section below.
    4.  _Compliance with Law and Our Own Obligations_. We may use the information we collected, to the extent permitted or required under applicable laws (i) to enforce our Terms of Service or other legal rights, including intellectual property infringement, (ii) to detect and protect against potentially prohibited or illegal activities, including fraud and unauthorized access, (iii) in response to lawful requests for information or legal process, (iv) to establish, exercise, or defend a legal claim, and (v) to comply with our contractual obligations, our policies, industry standards, and applicable laws.
    5.  _Other Purposes_. We may use the information we collect for other purposes for which we provide notice to you at the time of collection or for which we obtain your consent.
    6.  _Aggregate Data_. We may process your information in an anonymized or aggregated form for purposes other than described above.

* * *

  * ## Information Sharing

We may share Business Information, User Information, and General Information as follows:  

    1.  _Service Providers_. We may engage service providers to assist us in providing Services. These service providers may provide services such as fraud prevention, cloud computing, cybersecurity, identity verification, credit checks, collections, and payment processing. We may share any information we receive with such parties as is necessary for the provision of the Services.
    2.  _As Required By Law and Similar Disclosures_. We may disclose your information if we believe doing so is required or appropriate to (i) comply with applicable laws, regulations, and card association rules, (ii) comply with regulatory investigations, enforcement requests, and legal process, such as subpoenas, court orders, and bankruptcy notices, (iii) respond to your requests or resolve disputes or inquiries, (iv) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, confidentiality, security or technical issues, (v) respond to regulatory authorities jurisdiction over us for examinations, compliance, or other purposes, (vi) respond to requests from bank partners or third-party auditors, and (vii) protect your, our, or others’ rights, property, or safety, or the security or integrity of our Services.
    3.  _Business Partners_. We may disclose information about you with business partners in connection with jointly offered products and services, as well as products and services offered by these partners and made available through the Services or which we believe may be of interest to you or your business. These business partners are generally subject to contractual obligations entered into with us restricting how they may use this information.
    4.  _Corporate Changes_. We may disclose your information in connection with (including, without limitation, during the negotiation or due diligence process of) a corporate merger, consolidation, or restructuring; the sale of substantially all of our stock and/or assets; equity or debt financing, acquisition, divestiture, or dissolution of all or a portion of our business; or other corporate change.
    5.  _Aggregated or Anonymized Information_. We may sell, license or distribute information in anonymized or aggregated form so that the information does not identify a specific user, without restriction, including, but not limited to, for producing data analytics and reports for business partners or other third parties.
    6.  _Consent_. We may disclose your information to any third party with your consent. For example, we may disclose information at your direction, as described at the time you agree to share, or when you authorize a third-party application or website to access your information.
    7.  _Other Purpose_. To fulfill the purpose for which you provide such information to us or any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information to us.

* * *

  * ## Third-Party Information Collection

We may work with third-party advertising partners (e.g., Facebook) to display advertisements on the Sites and other websites and mobile applications and third-party analytics partners (e.g., Google Analytics) to evaluate and provide us with information regarding your use of the Sites. We may also utilize framing techniques to serve you content from third-party providers, while preserving the look and feel of the Services. In such cases, you will be providing information to these third-parties.

These third parties may use cookies, Web beacons, pixel tags and similar technologies to collect information about your activities on the Sites and other Web sites to provide you personalized advertising based on your interests and browsing activity. If you do not wish to receive interest-based ads, you may click [here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/) to learn more about how you may opt out. To opt out of certain interest-based advertising on your mobile device, iOS users can click [here](https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT205223) and Android users can click [here](https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662922?hl=en). In addition, you may be able to access settings offered by your mobile operating system to limit ad tracking or install the AppChoices application to learn more about how you may opt out of receiving personalized mobile ads. Please note that opting out of interest-based advertising does not limit all advertising.

* * *

  * ## Push Notifications

If you are a user of our applications, we may send push notifications or alerts to your mobile device even when you are not logged in. We may use push notifications to send you notifications related to the Services and various triggers based on your selections. You can manage your push notification preferences or deactivate these notifications by turning off notifications under settings for your mobile device. If you choose not to receive push notifications, you may still receive in-app notifications.

* * *

  * ## Your Access

If you are a registered user of the Services, you may review or modify certain Business Information and User Information we have collected about you by logging into your account for the Services and updating your profile. This section of the Site is password protected to better safeguard your information. If you would like to change any other information that you cannot independently correct, you may submit a request for such updates by contacting us at the address or phone number at the bottom of this Privacy Policy. Under certain circumstances we may not be able to fulfill your request, such as if it restricts our ability to comply with applicable laws and regulations or legal process, we cannot verify your identity, or it involves disproportionate cost or effort. In such instances, we will respond to your request within a reasonable timeframe and provide you an explanation of our decision.

* * *

  * ## Your Choices

You may choose to stop receiving marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails. You may also request that we do not call you for marketing-related purposes. In addition to following the unsubscribe instruction in relevant email communications, you may make these requests by contacting us at support@kabbage.com, calling us at 888-986-8263 or writing to us at Kabbage Customer Service P.O. Box 77073, Atlanta, GA 30357-1073, Attn: Marketing Opt-Out. We will respond to your request within a reasonable timeframe. In addition, if you no longer wish to receive marketing notifications through our mobile applications you can adjust your device's privacy preferences by visiting the settings page of the device. Opting out of marketing emails or notifications will not stop your receipt of non-marketing emails and notifications related to the Services.

Various browsers may offer their own tools to manage cookies. If you disable cookies, you can still use the Services, but your ability to use some features of the Services may be limited.

* * *

  * ## Links to Third Party Websites

The Sites may include links to other websites or mobile applications whose privacy practices may differ from ours. We are not responsible for any practices employed on third-party websites or applications, including the information and content contained on the website or application. If you submit information to a third-party website or application, your information is governed by the third party's privacy policy. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any website or application you visit, access, or use.

* * *

  * ## Security of Information

We take reasonable measures, including administrative, technical, and physical safeguards to protect your information from loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction. These security measures include firewalls, data encryption, physical access controls to our data centers, and information access authorization controls. Your information is securely sent to us with at least 128 bit-encryption over the Transport Layer Security (TLS) protocol. This creates an encrypted connection between your browser and us so that any sensitive information you provide can be securely transmitted. Unfortunately, the Internet cannot be guaranteed to be 100% secure, and we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you provide to us.

If you link your bank account information as a part of applying for or receiving the Services, we will have read-only access to such information. We do not have access to change, edit, or modify your bank account information. We also cannot see your banking credentials (i.e., username and passwords). You are responsible for securing and maintaining the privacy of your banking credentials and account information. We are not responsible for protecting any information we share with a third-party based on an account connection that you have authorized.

* * *

  * ## Children Under 13

This Site and products or services available through this Site are not intended for children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly solicit or market online to children under the age of 13. If we knowingly receive a child's personally identifiable information, we will immediately delete it from our system. Contact us at the address or phone number at the bottom of this Privacy Policy if you believe that we have mistakenly or unintentionally collected information from a child under the age of 13.

* * *

  * ## Testimonials

We may display testimonials of satisfied Customers on the Services with their consent. If you wish to update or delete a testimonial posted in accordance with this Privacy Policy, you can contact us at the address or phone number at the bottom of this Privacy Policy.

* * *

  * ## Referrals

If you choose to participate in a referral service program to tell a business about the Services, we will ask you for the business's name and email address. Depending on the Services used, we will send the referred business an email either directly or on behalf of our business or financial institution partners, inviting the business to use the Services. We store information about the business for the purpose of sending an email and tracking the success of the referral program. We may send additional emails to the business directly or on behalf of our business or financial institution partners, unless the business opts out of receiving such emails. Businesses that you refer may contact us at the address or phone number at the bottom of this this Privacy Policy to request that we remove their information from our database.

* * *

  * ## Social Media Widgets

The Services may include social media features and widgets, such as the Facebook “Like” button, or interactive mini-programs that run on the Services. These features may collect information such as your IP address and which page you are visiting on the Site and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third-party or hosted directly on the Services. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

* * *

  * ## Data Retention

We will retain your information for (i) as long as reasonably necessary to provide you Services, (ii) as long as reasonably useful for commercial purposes, or (iii) as long as necessary to comply with applicable laws and internal policies regarding recordkeeping, reporting, audits, and litigation holds. If you wish to request that we no longer use your information to provide you Services, you may contact us at the address or phone number at the bottom of this Privacy Policy. We will nonetheless retain your information to the extent that we deem necessary to comply with our legal or contractual obligations, resolve disputes, as needed to provide you Services, or for other business purposes.

* * *

  * ## Transfers to Other Countries

We may transfer information to other countries, for example, for customer service or to process transactions. We will protect your information as described in this Privacy Policy if your information is transferred to other countries. By using our Sites and Services, you consent to your information being transferred to other countries, including countries that have different data protection rules than your country. We do not represent that our Sites and Services are appropriate or available in any particular jurisdiction.

* * *

  * ## Changes to Privacy Policy

By visiting the Sites or using the Services, you accept the practices described in this Privacy Policy. We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time by making available a revised, dated version on the Sites. If the revised version includes a substantial change, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, an email notification of Privacy Policy changes) prior to the change becoming effective. Your continued use of the Site shall constitute your acceptance of such updated Privacy Policy. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

* * *

  * ## Contact Us

Any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, our practices, the Sites, or the Services, please contact us by at email support@kabbage.com or with a letter by postal mail to:

Kabbage, Inc.  
925B Peachtree Street NE, Suite 1688  
Atlanta, GA 30309

For phone inquiries please call: [888-986-8263](tel:+18889868263)

* * *

  * ## TRUSTe

If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based, third-party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at: <https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request>.

* * *

## Industry Policy

  *  _Kabbage_ does not provide credit access to businesses in the following industries: marijuana, CBD, gambling, financial institutions, lending or non-profit organizations. _Kabbage_ does not provide credit access to businesses that sell or manufacture any form of assault-style weapon/rifle, AND/OR sell firearms or ammunition to individuals under 21. Other businesses in the firearms industry are eligible to apply with _Kabbage_.

* * *

## See how much you qualify for today!
